

Dmitry Hrabrov

Indie game developer



5 October 1988



Belarus, Gomel



+375447606986



http://dexperix.net



soft@dexp.in

About me ———

I've been in the game development since 2014. The first game was made on the RenPy engine (Python language). Others were made in the pure C. I totally love C language and have been using it more than 10 years. The main skill is making crossplatform applications. My personal dream is to make fun computer games that people will like.

Skills ——— JavaScript Java C,C++,CGI MySQL **HTML** CSS,SASS XML

JQuery, Prototype.js

Linux

Education

2012-2016 Post-Graduation Course, IT Gomel State Technical University Research topics: Pseudorandom sequences generators on cellular automata; local Wi-Fi positioning.

Master of Engineering Science, IT 2011-2012 Gomel State Technical University 2006-2011 Bachelor of Science, IT **Gomel State Technical University** 2004-2006 Graduate Gomel state regional lyceum

Specializing in mathematics and Informatics, Olympiad programming Received knowledge: recursion, Dijkstra's algorithm, guick sort, hash

tables, minimal spanning tree, binary heap, etc.

Publications

More then 40 scientific publications in Russian. Including: 5 articles in scientific magazines, 4 patents, participation in competitions, many conferences materials.

Web Experience

2014-2015 Web developer

http://onemangaday.dexp.in

The website for One Manga Day game.

Technologies: Git, Jekyll, SASS, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript. Site and game sources: https://github.com/DeXP/onemangaday

2009-2012 PHP developer

https://livemaster.ru

Both front-end and back-end. Implementation of help-system with administration/moderation interface. AJAX picture uploading with image crop. Prototype.js patch for local bugs. Pixel-perfect HTML and CSS layout. Written PHP and JavaScript code lines: \sim 10k. Technologies: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, AJAX, Prototype.js, HTML,

CSS, memcached.

2005-2011 Web developer http://dexperix.net

Old personal website. The engine is self-made, written in C++. Info

stored in MySQL, with LaTeX-like syntaxis.

Used technologies: C++, MySQL, LaTeX, HTML, CSS.

Other Experience

2014-2017 Game Developer http://store.steampowered.com/search/?developer=DeXP

Steam games: One Manga Day, Winter Novel, Wordlase.

Technologies: Python, C, RenPy, JSON, XML, gzip, PNG, OGG, libc,

SDL, WinAPI, Linux, Mac OS X, steamworks.

2012-2017 Teacher at Gomel State Technical University https://www.gstu.by

> Assistance in the following courses: Lisp, AI, Algorithmization, Object-oriented programming, Java, CAD-systems, Databases, Oper-

ation systems, Networks, Cloud computing.

Teaching at University's Android game development course.

2012-2014 Hardware developer

https://www.gstu.by

Working directly with flash memory, USB protocol, Pic8 controllers, STM ARM controllers, Xilinx FPGA. The same code worked on Linux,

Windows and Pic-controller. Technologies: C, C++, VHDL, Qt.

Interests: Linux, Games, Programming, Hardware, Fantasy books, Martial arts. Languages: Russian (native), English (upper-intermediate), Belarusian (native). For more detailed information see my LinkedIn profile.

Links

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dexperix

GitHub: https://github.com/DeXP

Steam: http://steamcommunity.com/id/dexp

Games: http://store.steampowered.com/search/?developer=DeXP

Google Play: https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?id=7932817826050175353